# Eduardo Elías Chacón

# Web Developer

Buenos Aires, Argentina | +54 9 11 33564337 | eduardo.elias.1192@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/eduardoe92/ | https://eduardoeliaschacon-portfolio.vercel.app/

### **Professional Profile:**

Professional with experience in web development. Known for advanced technical skills in web programming, using relevant technologies. Focused on customer satisfaction and process optimization. Capable of combining software development knowledge with strong technical support experience to provide effective solutions.

### **Education:**

### FULL STACK DEVELOPER CORE | OCT 2023 - MAY 2024 | DIGITAL NAO X TECMILENIO

- Front End (User-facing interfaces and systems)
- Back End (Logic, servers, and databases)

### DEVELOPER FULL STACK | DEC 2022 - SEPT 2023 | EGG COOPERATION

- · Introduction to programming, Java, MySQL databases, and React.js.
- · Object-oriented programming, exception handling and database connections.

### WEB DEVELOPER FRONT END | MARCH 2022 - JUNE 2023 | EIDOS GLOBAL - ACCENTURE

- · Strengthen skills in technologies with the aim of enhancing development.
- · HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and GitHub.

### **Work Experience:**

#### **DEVELOPER FRONT END | IGROWKER | JUNE 2024 – JULY 2024**

- · Development of a Mobile First web app to manage events efficiently.
- Ensure the technical and commercial viability of the project, generating impact and growth in the skills of developers.

### DEVELOPER FRONT END | MAKISAN TECH | JUNE 2023 - DEC 2024

- · Development and maintenance of applications and web pages.
- · Improve user experience and optimize project performance.

#### CUSTOMER SERVICE AND SUPPORT | MOVILNET - MANPOWER | SEPT 2013 - FEB 2017

Resolution of queries and technical problems, sales, promotions, account management, complaint handling, case tracking, achievement of objectives and telecommunications service.

## **Technical Knowledge:**

Java | React JS | Java Script | Astro | Node JS | Spring MVC | HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | Tailwind-CSS | MySQL | GitHub | Postman | Wordpress | Jira | Trello | Notion | Miro | Figma | Vercel.

#### Skill Set:

Systems management | Process optimization | IT consulting and assistance | Customer service | Quality control | Technical Support | Effective Communication | Adaptability | Attention to details | Time management | Creativity | Logical and analytical thinking | Teamwork.

# Languajes:

- · Spanish: Native.
- · English: A1-A2.